150 minutes of exercise a week: that's how much we should all be doing.
每周150分钟的运动：这是我们都应该达到的运动量。
Does this mean that gyms are the best ways to guarantee our health?
这是否意味着去健身房锻炼是保证我们健康的最佳方式？
Maybe, but they are not without their own health risks.
也许吧，但它们本身也并非没有健康风险。
Recent studies have suggested that some gym-goers' hygiene standards leave much to be desired.
最近的研究表明，一些健身房锻炼爱好者的卫生标准差强人意。
Bacteria that can cause serious illness, such as food poisoning or pneumonia, was found on the surface of gym equipment.
在健身器材表面发现了可导致严重疾病（如食物中毒或肺炎）的细菌。
Sweat and the increased temperature caused by exercise can help dangerous bacteria grow on the skin, which can be transferred to our clothing.
汗水以及运动引起的体温升高会助长危险细菌在皮肤上生长，这些细菌可以转移到我们的衣物上。
It might not just be the microbes at a gym that could be toxic.
可能不仅仅健身房里的微生物是有害的。
Toxic gym culture may be leading people to feel judged or intimidated.
有毒的健身房文化可能会让人们感到被评判或受到威胁。
In a 2019 US study, over half those surveyed felt anxious when going to the gym.
在2019年美国的一项研究中，超过一半的受访者在去健身房时感到焦虑。
This feeling of being judged, and an overly competitive atmosphere, could create pressure to over-exercise.
这种被评判的感觉以及过度竞争的氛围，可能会产生过度运动的压力。
The Cleveland Clinic distinguishes between overreaching and over-training.
克利夫兰诊所区分了过度努力和过度训练。
The first is the result of a single instance of over-exertion, which leads to little more than muscle soreness, while the latter is more long-term and can have more serious consequences.
前者是单次过度劳累的结果，只会导致肌肉酸痛，而后者则更长期，可能产生更严重的后果。
Over-training has been linked to injuries, fatigue, reduced appetite and problems with sleep or weight gain.
受伤、疲劳、食欲下降以及睡眠问题或体重增加都与过度训练有关。
When exercise becomes a compulsion, it can also be dangerous for our mental health.
当运动成为一种强迫行为时，它也可能对我们的心理健康构成威胁。
Writing for CNET, wellness writer Taylor Leamey warns that feeling guilt at missed gym sessions or trying to use exercise as a way to control our bodies could be signs that exercise dependency is a problem.
健康作家泰勒·利米在CNET上撰文警告说，因错过健身课程而感到内疚，或试图将运动作为控制身体的一种方式，可能是运动成瘾问题的迹象。
This can be linked with having a negative body image.
这可能与负面的身体形象（过度关注体型）有关。
Of course, we shouldn't forget that exercise can really help our physical and mental health, as long as we can maintain a healthy relationship with it.
当然，我们不应忘记，只要我们能与之保持健康的关系，运动确实有助于我们的身心健康。